Michal Nawrocki

64 Warwards Lane, B29 7RD Birmingham, United Kingdom 07596 246076

michal.m.nawrocki@gmail.com <u>linkedin.com/in/michal-m-nawrocki</u> github.com/michal-nawrocki www.nawrocki.dev

Profile

Final year computer science multilingual student at the University of Birmingham with a big understanding of software development, graphic design, and passion for self-improvement, ready to tackle any problem and continue his self-taught programming journey

Volunteering

Treasurer of Polish Society // 2017-2018 University of Birmingham, UK

Was responsible for managing the funding of the society (collecting membership fees from new members, applying for grants). Took care of budgeting and organising events such as cooking classes, BBQ hangouts.

References

John Morris

Simulation Lead Developer Yobota, London, UK john@yobota.xyz

Interests





Synthwave music



Photography



Travelling



Sci-Fi Movies



Cooking



Technical skills

Languages Tools Platforms/OS JetBrains, Visual Studio, Python, Java, C/C++, AWS, Heroku, C#, SQL, JS, Haskell, VS Code, Git, Ansible, Confluence, JIRA, HTML/CSS, OpenGL Docker, Jenkins, Latex Linux, Mac, Win

Main areas of experience

- Object-oriented programming
- Data Structures
- 3D Graphics
- · Graphic design
- Networking

- Software engineering
- Test-driven development
- · Embedded systems
- Algorithms
- Web services

Education

MSci Computer Science with an Industrial Year // 2016 - Current University of Birmingham, UK

Noticeable third-year modules: Operating Systems (65), Networks (71), Mobile computing with Android (67), Network Security (72), Intelligent Robotics (79)

Average: 71 (First-class mark)

Noticeable second-year modules (mark): C/C++ (66), Haskell (58), Game Development Team Project (76), 3D Graphics (54), Databases (71)

Average: 64 (Upper Second-class mark)

Noticeable first-year modules: Software Engineering (90), Robot Programming (95), Java Software Workshop (90), Data Structures and Algorithms (78), Mathematics (73)

Average: 72 (First-class mark)

International Baccalaureate Diploma Programme // 2013 - 2016 Zespol Szkol Ogolnokstalcacy nr 10 in Gliwice, Poland

Noticeable subjects (out of 7): Computer Science HL (6), Mathematics (5) Final Mark: 35/45

Work experience

Software Developer (part-time) // September 2020 - Current Yobota, London, UK (remote work)

Continued working remotely on projects that I've started in my placement. Took part in different projects and PODs (i.e. staff API). Improved the Django staff app with new features and endpoints. Rewrote documents manager to use S3 buckets. Automated sim results as Google Sheets for clients.

Industrial placement // July 2019 - September 2020 Yobota, London, UK

Expanded functionality of a simulation framework used to predict the behaviour of the company's in-house banking platform, written using Django. Containerized services using Heroku, AWS, Docker and Ansible. Wrote documentation on the codebase. Fixed bugs in the banking platform's staff app. Made Jenkins pipelines. Automate tasks of the sim.

Game development group project // Spring 2018 University of Birmingham, UK

Created a UDP client-server infrastructure for a Java based air traffic control simulator computer game. Refactored and optimised game logic code to allow for multiplayer versus mode. Collaborated on the renderer section of the game engine using OpenGL. Documented and demonstrated software to a publisher.